to quit. Not hardly.
side day yard work so what's the morning
I don't care
I don't care anything
I don't care about it
No
You know, Braum Panna, I don't like you
I think you're a two-faced piece of snake
piece of shit
You're cut
Have a good night man go with all these rumble and talk to them. Why plays gt5?
You're cut you're cut man
Sorry you're cut
Not my fault it's your fault
Listen, this is not drama, this is me, John.
This is me, John.
I'll make a burger, I'll eat a burger.
I'll be a shitty burger, but it'll still be a burger.
I don't know what's wrong with your brain
This is not meant to be old drama drama this drama that nobody cares about that
I see fucking
Something wrong with your brain
You're dysfunctionally disabled
It's your mental illness. No, I give a shit about drama
It's never been about drama man
This is always supposed to be about people having fun laughing and talking to each other.
All right, you're fucking screwed in the head.
I don't think it's funny, but
their idea is funny, it's not the same as mine.
I sure might be slightly rotten, but
I'm gonna heat it up until it cooks,
and then I'm gonna cook it again.
Just kill all the bacteria.
Smells a little fishy
And we shall see
Things can be seen till they're not seen they're seen they're seen
I should do that.
That's all there is.
You guys are monkeys, uh, no, or anything.
I know we just got something smart to say no.
Hmm, I figured that would happen.
Well, I'm gonna go to bed here in about two hours.
And chill out.
I don't think that was rotten, so.
I should probably be able to get the humans rotten up, but my gut can handle it.
What's the worst gonna happen? I'm gonna get shits.
Yeah, sounds fine.
I know you're all a little in discord, faggots.
I'm already tired.
Gangs are angry people
Don't want to hate people. I already know that
I'm a stupid. Been around the block probably many more times than you have
See you more time
Yeah, I'm gonna cook this shit out of the shrub
I don't know if it's even out above up my body can handle it. I think it might be slightly sour
And it might as well eat it though while I have
The hole is in this bag, and those are two beers, okay.
Got a couple of beers.
I ain't keep going, man.
Oh, that's stupid.
Stupid is, the stupid does.
What it was, it's not because.
It's a unique language
All right, well, you know the stream is very done
I mean for you now, I'm gonna probably later. I'm gonna sleep. I'll play Star Wars for like maybe an hour
And it'll piss me the whole off
No, I even like this guy fucking brown paint is a weirdo man
One of his issues is change his name from Bob Pandit or Lowrider65, uh, yeah, he's definitely
I'm just gonna cook the hell out of this fucking shrimp
I might be slay you right now
I'm gonna eat the hell out of it
You know why? Cause I want you
And it won't kill me
It won't fucking kill me
I don't care about people being Mexican
He's not even Mexican, he's South American right?
I made you no matter how far that highway goes
An old dirt road to get you home
Come on!
If you see it in the ride when they try to live
You the bullet hole in a stop sign
Kind that I'm right there with you
Put your drinks up high for my country phone
My country phone
I'm out here
I
It's very simple, and a simple plan.
I'm cooking about 5 pounds of shrimp.
Starting to smoke.
Okay, okay, bye.
I'm washing up.
Throw out my yard
Smoke a little bit
You know none these people like each other, right?
None of these people actually like each other
They all want to think somebody's more stupid and retarded in there
That's a funny part of it.
That's all funny, that's all the way, I suppose.
I'm thinking it's hilarious when you make it hilarious.
Everything being made funny in its own way.
Smoking
Yeah, so
So I'll seem retarded
Yes, I'm weird, but like
Just feel see my third fucking retarded man
We'll stop the smoke stop burn off the fat
I ain't food poisoning. It doesn't actually hurt me.
My body is too strong for it.
I ain't smell a shrimp. I want to smell it amazingly amazing.
Might not be that great, but
I'll still eat it
I'll put it through the ringer
All right, anybody live right now? No, nobody's live
Nobody's live
See who's live? Ujic user's live. I'm done with live streaming making no money
Wow, should I just like copy that for my next stream?
Cuz I got back to Vegas. I've been sick
Maybe allergies from Spokane, Washington
But probably just I don't know what I'm gonna focus on getting a regular job
I'm gonna focus on getting a regular job. So I'm fucking done
Look look this shit. Let me get rid of this
Everybody else makes fucking money. I have to fucking collect coupons. I have to fucking collect coupons to go fucking shopping
Fuck you. I'm done. I'm ending the fucking stream. It's I just wanted to fucking just go live really quickly
So you motherfuckers know what's up with me. I'm not
He says this once a week. I'm not a stream anymore because nobody donates
It's one of the dumbest griffs on the face of earth because no be back in two days
Streaming anymore. I'm not live streaming anymore. I'm fucking done. I make no fucking money. So that's why I'm fucking done
You're done
Awesome there, buddy
Could even raise the money
Goodbye I'm ending a bye
Fuck you, you piece...
Well, he's mad that he yells at people to give money.
Should I start doing that?
So we go on, we are AMS.
Is that a good grift?
We go on Tuesday for the matinee.
What the fuck?
The Tuesday drops the price.
The matinee drops the price.
AMC member drops the price.
I know, I'm going to use some rotten shrimp, but I'm cooking it thoroughly first.
to try to kill any bacteria
so og user is done for the like the fucking five thousandth time
saying nobody donates to him give me money or i won't stream
it's very nice grift i suppose
It's interesting
It's just him being him
My house smells like rotten shrimp
I'm gonna eat all your shit
to make it very crispy.
Zimbabweos live right now.
Okay, these are trolls.
YouTube's dead man
Everything is dead
People I think people are starting to finally get bored with it or not
Should I agree with I agree with 100%
So
No, I'm bored. This is boring
No, don't show this
Yeah, that's many now YouTube 150 million warnings